# **Marjorie Yang**

## **Undergraduate Student**

Expected Completion: December 2023

Solutions-oriented undergraduate student with a passion for the intersection between design and technology. Proven track record in a diverse range of experience in design and media, delivering value in leadership, diligence, problemsolving, and her extensive set of technical skills as well.

### **Experience**

#### 2022-10 -Present

### Web Designer & Developer (Part-time)

Covid-19 Impact Project, NYU Tisch

- Conduct user experience research on the current site.
- Plan an appropriate redesign based on the research creating a wireframe, sitemap, and prototype in the process.
- Work with content and media asset producers to build the redesigned site using WordPress.

#### 2022-03 -2022-12

#### **Networks Assistant (Part-time)**

SiteSeers Team, NYU Tisch - ITP Department

- Worked with a team to develop websites for the ITP department using WordPress.
- Assisted with design ideation and implementation using Figma.
- Implemented improvements for accessibility on different projects.

#### 2022-06 -2022-10

### **Creative Director, Researcher, and Developer**

Rising - Immersive Game Installation, NYU Grant

- · Designed the game's UI.
- Developed and designed game interactivity using Unity, Adobe mixamo, and Python.

#### 2019-07 -2019-08

#### **Graphic Design Intern**

Hengdu Law Firm (Beijing, China)

- Designed print materials such as brochures that are used for conventions in the US.
- · Assisted in translating marketing materials.
- Designed potential logos and corresponding merchandise packages.

### **Education**

#### 2020-09 -2023-12

#### **BFA in Interactive Media Arts (3.8 GPA)**

New York University, Tisch School of the Arts Minors: Computer Science & Environmental Studies Honors & Awards: Dean's List (past 2 years), \*This Is

Not A Drill\* Research Grant

### 2016-09 -2020-06

### **International Baccaulaureate Diploma**

Dulwich College Beijing, High School

Honors & Awards: Pearson GCSE Highest Mark in China for Art & Design, Community Prefect, Graeme Salte Award for Innovation, Pioneering Spirit Grant

### **Conferences**

#### **Personal Info**

Address 429 E 6th St New York, NY 10009

Phone +1 (646) 206-4434

Email my2211@nyu.edu

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/ marjorie-yang-000/

#### Skills

#### Leadership

Communication

Interface Design

Front-End Development Sitemap and Wireframing

**User Stories** 

#### **English**

Chinese (Mandarin)

#### **Volunteer Work**

## **Co-founder of Guangai Hope** Project (Beijing, China) 2019

Provided the understaffed Guangai elementary school in with student volunteers.

**Volunteer in New Hope** Orphanage (Beijing, China) 2016-2019